# Kenneth Ekandem

## Software Engineer

Address Uyo, Akwa Ibom, 520261

**Phone** 09067170010

E-mail kennyekandem@gmail.com

**Twitter** https://twitter.com/Kenneth\_Ekandem **LinkedIn** https://www.linkedin.com/in/kenneth-ekandem-66a73a

Lead Back End Developer at Codekago Interactive with over four years of successful experience in PHP and Javascript programming. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success. Strengths in PHP and Javascript and other skills backed by training in Codekago Interactive and finally becoming a staff.

#### Skills

Collaborative Leadership

Team-oriented and dependable

Laravel PHP

PHP

Lumen PHP

Node JS

**Express JS** 

Adonis JS

Firebase for NoSQL

Google Cloud Services

Digital Ocean Setup and configuration

Payment Integration using Paypal, Stripe and Paystack.

Team leader

### **Work History**

2020-05 - Current

### Lead Back End Developer

Codekago Interactive, uyo, Akwa Ibom

As the Lead Back End Developer, I handle all Back End related projects in the company, evaluated codes, in charge code review and deployment. I'm also in charge of handling all online services in relation to web and application development.

2020-01 - 2020-05

Senior Back End Developer

Codekago Interactive, Uyo, Akwa Ibom

As a senior Back End developer, I was involved in majority of the projects at Codekago that involved implementing a back end language for better usability. Was also in charge on online panel configurations for hosting and deployment for most projects.

#### **Education**

#### 2020-01 - Current Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

University Of Uyo - Uyo, Akwa Ibom

#### **Interests**

Game Development

Learning Andriod and IOS application Development

Learning programming languages that will influence the future of programming

#### **Hobbies**

I like coding, watching movies, have tech talks and reading novels.